let quiz   =[
    {question: "Is 84 Even or Odd ? ",
option:[
    "Ever",
    "Odd",
    "Both Even and Odd",
    "None of these",

],
answer:1, 
},

{
    question: "How do you write this number using Digit?   'Nine Hundred and Sixty One." ,
option:[
    91,
    961,
    9061,
    90061,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "In 3791, the place value of 7 is _____. ",
option:[
    "Thousands",
    "Hundreds",
    "Ones",
    "Tens",

],
answer:2, 
},
{question: "Find the missing number in this sequence 532,542,__,562.",
option:[
    522,
    525,
    552,
    572,

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "What comes just after 435?",
option:[
    434,
    436,
    437,
    433,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "Four Hundred and one can be written in digit as ______.",
option:[
    41,
    411,
    4001,
    401,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "What is 200 more than 646?",
option:[
    746,
    846,
    946,
    1046,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "Put these numbers in order from smallest to largest. '85' ,'56' ,'65'" ,
option:[
    "56,65,85",
    "56,85,65",
    "65,85,56",
    "85,65,56",


],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "How many whole weeks are in a month?",
option:[
    3,
    4,
    5,
    6,

],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "11.50+10.20 = ____?",
option:[
    21.50,
    22,
    20.70,
    21.70,

],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "I am odd number.I have 8 on tens place. I am greater than 81 but less than 85. What is am I? ",
option:[
    81,
    84,
    82,
    83,

],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "I have a 1 in the ones place. I am greater than 41 but less than 57. What number am I?",
option:[
    41,
    44,
    51,
    50,

],
answer:3, 
},
{
    question: "1 Fortnight=__ days? ",
option:[
    10,
    12,
    15,
    20,

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "How many days does month August have?",
option:[
    31,
    29,
    30,
    28,

],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "How many days does month February have?",
option:[
    31,
    29,
    30,
    28,

],
answer:4, 
}]